A Guide to the Rodman C. Rockefeller papers FA1350
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Cultural Interests, 1969-2001; II; 5.59 Cubic Feet 11 letter document boxes and 3 legal document boxes
  - Museums - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1985-1990 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Monticello Correspondence, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Monticello Correspondence, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Monticello Correspondence, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Monticello Correspondence, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Monticello Correspondence, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Monticello Correspondence, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Monticello Correspondence, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Monticello Correspondence, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Monticello Correspondence, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Monticello Correspondence, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Monticello Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Monticello: International Center for Jefferson Studies, 1995-1999 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Monticello: Jefferson Symposium Correspondence, London, England, 1999 September 23 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Monticello: Campaign for Monticello Statement of Program Objectives 1993 -1995, 1992 November (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Monticello: The International Center for Jefferson Studies: Discussion Papers, 1993 January (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Monticello: Evening Conversations at Monticello - Correspondence, 1998 August 18-October 1 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Monticello: Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation - Medal for Architecture, 1987-2000 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Monticello: Global Outreach Program, 1997-1998 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Monticello: Board Meeting - Charlottesville Itinerary, 1996 October 31-November 2 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Monticello: Steering Committee Meetings, 1994; 1996 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Monticello: New York Committee, 1993; 1995 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Monticello: Biographical Material (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Monticello: Biographical Material Campaign Leaders (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Monticello: Historical Sketch of the Foundation and Thomas Jefferson (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Monticello: Loan Proposals for Monticello Artifacts, 1993-1997 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Monticello: Acquisitions and Loans, 1993-1997 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Monticello: Fundraising, 1993-1999 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Monticello: Thomas Jefferson's 250th Birthday Celebration and Capital Campaign, 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Monticello: Pamphlets and Articles (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation - Correspondence, 1992-1998 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - National Audobon Society - General Files - Organizations, 1991-1995 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Rockefeller Tavern Correspondence, 1981-1994 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Rockefeller Tavern Correspondence, 1983-1994 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller Tavern - Bank Account, 1992-1993 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - The Royal Society for the Encouragement of Arts, Manufacturers, and Commerce - The Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation, and The English -Speaking Union of the Commonwealth, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - San Antonio Museum of Art - NAR Wing Opening Night, 1998 October 22 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - U.S. - Mexico Commission By-Laws, 1995-1996 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - U.S. - Mexico Commission Board Meetings, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - U.S. - Mexico Commission Board Meetings, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - U.S. - Mexico Commission Work Study Program, 1996-1997 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - U.S. - Mexico Commission Agreement, September, 1991 November (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - U.S. - Mexico Commission - Annual Reports, 1994-1996 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - U.S. - Mexico Commission - Correspondence, 1995 January-June (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - U.S. - Mexico Commission - Correspondence, 1995 August-December (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - U.S. - Mexico Commission - Correspondence, January -June 1996, 1996 January-June (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - U.S. - Mexico Commission - Correspondence, 1996 January-June (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - U.S. - Mexico Commission - Correspondence, July - December 1996, 1996 July-December (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - U.S. - Mexico Commission - Correspondence, January -May 1997, 1997 January-May (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - U.S. - Mexico Commission - Correspondence, June - December 1997, 1997 June-December (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - U.S. - Mexico Commission Board Meeting, November 12 -14, 1997, 1997 November 12-14 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - U.S. - Mexico Commission, Correspondence, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - U.S. - Mexico Commission, Board Meeting, May 22, 1998, 1998 May 22 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - U.S. - Mexico Commission Board Meeting, November 13, 1998, 1998 November 13 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - U.S. - Mexico Commission Advisory Committee, 1997 -1998 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - U.S. - Mexico Commission Advisory Committee, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - U.S. - Mexico Commission Advisory Committee, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - U.S. - Mexico Commission Correspondence, January -June 1999, 1999 January-June (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - U.S. - Mexico Commission - Adriana Arzac Contracts 1994 - Resignation 1996, 1994-1996 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - U.S. - Mexico Commission - Washington Fulbright Workshop, May 15 -27, 1994, 1994 May 15-27 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - U.S. - Mexico Commission Annual Program Plan, 1994 -1996, 1997, 1994-1997 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - U.S. - Mexico Commission Correspondence, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - U.S. - Mexico Commission Correspondence, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - U.S. - Mexico Commission Correspondence, January -June 1994, 1994 January-June (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - U.S. - Mexico Commission Correspondence, July - December 1994, 1994 July-December (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - U.S. - Mexico Cultural Commission - U.S. Council, September 26 -27, 1991, 1991 September 26-27 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Educational/Cultural Luncheon, September 27, 1991, 1991 September 27 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - U.S. - Mexico Commission for Education and Cultural Affiars - Board Members (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - U.S. - Mexico Commission Annual Reports and Pamphlets (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - U.S. - Mexico Commission for Educational and Cultural Exchange - Brief History, Program Activities and Data Information (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - U.S. - Mexico Commission for Educational and Cultural Exchange - Annual Program Report, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Thomas Jefferson Foundation, Monticello, 1994-1999 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - United Fund - Red Cross Dinner, Akron, Ohio, 1969 August 7 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Monticello Annual Dinner in Honor of Lord Richard Rogers, Monticello, 1999 April 12 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Remarks at Jefferson Cabinet, Monticello, Virginia, 1998 June 5 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Remarks for the Monticell Dinner, New York, 1998 May 7 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Remarks for the Cabinet Retreat, Monticell, 1996 June 8 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Mr. Jefferson's Legacy, 1995 August (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - "Monticello as Economic Unit" Remarks at Monticello Cabinet Meeting, Charlottesville, VA, 1995 June 10 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Monticello Trustee Dinner, Pocantico Hills, NY, 1994 October 7 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - 251st Anniversary of the Birth of Thomas Jefferson (Speech), 1994 April 13 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Remarks at Scripps Dinner of 250th Birthday of TJ (Speech), 1993 February 28 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Impressions of Galapagos, 1992 July 13 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Ground Breaking at James Monroe House, Washington D.C., 1988 June 9 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Mr. Jefferson's Legacy, 1985 August 1 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Westchester County Tricentennial Dinner, Rye Hilton Hotel, New York, 1983 April 23 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Mexico - Aguila Azteca Award Correspondence, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Mexico - Aguila Azteca Award Dinner Guest List (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Mexico - Aguila Azteca Press Clippings (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Mexico - Articles re. Mexico (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Mexico - Fernando Barbachano (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Brazilian Documentary, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Brazil - Venezuela Trip 1972 Press Comments (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Mexican Cultural Institute (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Mexican Contacts (Names, Addresses etc.) (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - A Brief History of the Rockefeller Tavern and Surrounding Property 1740-1986 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Monticello Photographs, 1994 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Monticello Correspondence, 1992 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation Correspondence, 1995 (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - Monticello Dinner at the River Club, 1993 October 6 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Monticello - Fundraising (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - The International Council of the Museum of Modern Art: Spring Meeting, 1986 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - The International Council of the Museum of Modern Art: Spring Meeting, 1988 (Box 83, Folder 6)
- Personal Interests, 1929-2005; III; 14.41 Cubic Feet 32 letter document boxes, 2 legal document boxes, and 1 record storage box
  - Carriage Association - Conference Carriage Restoration and Preservation Competition, Charlottesville, Virginia, 1990 April 25 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Aspen Colorado Ski Trip, 1990 March 25-31 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Trip Itinerary - Lexington, Virginia, 1989 May 4-7 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Trip Itinerary, March 9 -14, 1990, Geneva, Switzerland - March 9 -12, 1990, London, England - March 12 -14, 1990, 1990 March (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Trip to Orlando, Florida, 1989 November 8-11 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Trip to North East Harbor Maine - Birchcroft, 1989 August 8-September 2 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Trip to Alta, Utah, 1989 March 19-24 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Dartmouth Reunion Dinner -Playhouse - Tarrytown, New York, 1988 October 1 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Trip to London (Itinerary Suggestions), 1988 July 4-10 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Family Services of Westchester Benefit - Scarbourough, New York, 1988 June 1 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Trip to Alta, Utah, 1988 March 31-April 6 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Family Christmas Lunch, 1987 December 13 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Peter Rockefeller's Rehearsal Dinner -Playhouse, 1987 December 18 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Peter Rockefeller's Engagement Party - Winterburn Farm, 1987 October 30 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Trip to Frankfurt, Germany - Itinerary, 1987 August 19-22 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Trip to Easthampton, Long Island, New York - Itinerary, 1987 August 17-30 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Mary C. Rockefeller's 80th Birthday Party Celebration in Maine, 1987 June 18-21 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Family Trip to London, Istanbul, and Greece, 1986 September 10-28 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Renaissance Weekend - New Years, Hilton Head and Savannah, Georgia, 1984 December 28-1985 January 1 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Jose Clemente Orozco: A Symposium Dartmouth College, 1984 October 12-13 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Ski Trip to Sun Valley Idaho, 1983 March 4-11 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Mary C. Rockefeller's 75th Birthday - JY Ranch, Wyoming, 1982 June 22-July 1 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Trip to Gstaad, Switzerland and Paris, France, 1982 January 22-February 1 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Trip to Gstaad, Switzerland and Paris, France, 1982 January 22-February 1 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - New Years Eve Renaissance Weekend, Hilton Head Island, South Carolina, 1981 December 29-1982 January 2 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Honeymoon in Mauna Kei, Hawaii (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Sir Alex Alexander's 70th Birthday, Trip to England and Frankfurt, Germany (Itinerary), 1986 November 17-22 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Northwest CARE Annual Seminar - Vancouver Salmon Farming, Victoria, Canada, 1988 October 25-30 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Caneel Bay Resort, Virgin Islands, 2000 January (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Trip to London, England and Frankfurt, Germany, 1999 September 21-25 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Laurels Horse Show - Unionville, Pennsylvania, 1999 September 10-12 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Hinckley Crewed Charters, 1999 February-June (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Allen Cottage Trip - Seal Harbor, Maine, 1999 August 9-September 3 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Carriage Drive, 1999 June 7 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Ski Trip to Vail, Colorado, 1999 February 25-March 7 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - JY Ranch - Jackson Hole, Wyoming, 1999 July 2-7 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Phelps Champagne Ball - Rye Brook, New York, 1999 May 1 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - London Trip, 1999 January 26-31 (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - Phelps Reception at the Playhouse, 1998 November 15 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - World Equestrian Games, 1998 September 30-October 12 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Trip to the Netherlands and Germany, 1998 August 8-27 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - United States Equestrian Team - Festival of Champions, 1998 June 18-21 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Horse Show at Southern Pines, North Carolina, 1998 April 8-13 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Horse Show at Southern Pines, North Carolina, 1998 April 8-13 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Ski Trip to Vail, Colorado, 1998 March 15-22 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Horse Show - Fairhill, Maryland, 1997 October 24-26 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Myopia Driving Event - South Hamilton, Massachusetts, 1997 October 9-12 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Gladstone Driving Event, 1997 September 25-28 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Bohemian Grove Trip - San Francisco, California, 1997 July 17-20 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Pocantico Carriage Drive, 1997 June 2 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Trip to China with American History Museum (Box 37, Folder 13-14)
  - Trip to Vail, Colorado, 1997 March 1-8 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Trip to Europe - Metzler Bank, 1997 January 11-24 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - CAA Annual Conference - Shelburne, Vermont, 1996 October 13-16 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Gladstone Driving Event, 1996 September 26-29 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Mexico - Aguila Aztec Award Dinner, Mexico City, 1996 March 11 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Highland Farms Trip - Millbrook, New York, 1995 September 16-17 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - New York Blood Center Dinner - New York, New York, 1995 June 13 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - New York Blood Center Dinner - New York, New York, 1995 June 13 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Carriage Drive - Chadds Ford, Pennsylvania - Brandywine, 1995 May 5-7 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Carriage Drive - Chadds Ford, Pennsylvania - Brandywine, 1995 May 5-7 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - West Palm Beach Trip, 1995 March 10-12 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Cousin's Dinner at Playhouse, 1999 June 18 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Carriage Drive - Pocantico, New York, 1994 June 6 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Seal Harbor, Maine (Itinerary), 1994 May 27-31 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Carriage Drive, Chadd Ford, Pennsylvania, 1994 May 6-8 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Trip to Florida - West Palm Beach, 1994 March 11-13 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Trip to England and Switzerland, 1994 February 2-12 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - World Pair Driving Championships - Gladstone, New Jersey, 1993 October 8-10 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - Dartmouth 40 Year Reunion Dinner - Pocantico, New York, 1993 October 2 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Trip to Burlington, Vermont - Northeast Kingdom, 1993 September 24-26 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Carriage Drive in Pocantico, 1993 June 7 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - 11th Annual Americas Society Spring Party (Itinerary), 1991 June 4 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - June Cousin's Weekend, 1991 June 14-16 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Carriage Drive, Winterburn Farms, New York, 1991 June 4 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Carriage Drive - Lexington, Kentucky, 1991 May 22-25 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Carriage Drive - Lexington, Kentucky, 1991 May 22-25 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Steven C. Rockefeller and Barbara Bellow's Wedding, Cornwall, Vermont, 1991 May 11 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Carriage Drive - Chadds Ford, Pennsylvania, 1991 May 3-5 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - New Years Renaissance Weekend - Hilton Head Island, South Carolina, 1990 December 25-1991 January 2 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Trip to England, 1990 November 7-12 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Mary C. Rockefeller's Fellowships Celebration, 25th Anniversary - Massachusetts, Virginia, 1990 October 12-14 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Northeast Harbor, Maine - "Birchcroft" Summer Home, 1989 December 14-1990 February 15 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Northeast Harbor, Maine - "Birchcroft" Summer Home, 1989-1990 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Trip to Equestrian Games in Geneva and Stockholm, 1990 July 21-29 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Trip to Tuscon, Arizona, 1991 December 27-1992 January 1 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Trip to Aspen, Colorado, 1992 March 1-8 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Trip to London, Geneva and Frankfurt, 1992 March 22-29 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Cousin's Weekend at Winrock Farms - Business Meeting, 1992 April 3-5 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Royal Windsor Horse Show, 1992 May 12-17 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Trip to the Galapagos Islands, Ecuador (Rodman C. Rockefeller's 60th Birthday), 1992 July 3-14 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Trip to Hanover, New Hampshire (Flight Itinerary), 1992 June 12-14 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Vacation in Seal Harbor, Maine, 1992 August 8-24 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Trip to London and Frankfurt (Itinerary), 1992 November 25-December 2 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Trip Itinerary to Charlotte, North Carolina (Pleasant Valley Promenade) and Charlottesville, Virginia (Monticello), 1993 January 14-17 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Trip to Palm Beach, Florida, 1993 February 27-March 1 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Hudson Valley House Tour, 1992 September 19-20 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Trip to Northeast Harbor, Maine - Trip on the "Night Train", 1991 August 15-31 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Trip to Northeast Harbor, Maine - Trip on the "Night Train", 1991 August 15-31 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Phelps Memorial Hospital - Champagne Ball - Honoring the Rockefeller family, 1991 November 16 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - New York Blood Center: Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - New York Blood Center: Correspondence, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - New York Blood Center: Correspondence, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - New York Blood Center: Correspondence, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - New York Blood Center: Correspondence, 1997 (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - New York Blood Center: Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - New York Blood Center: Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1995 October 18 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - New York Blood Center: Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1996 October 23 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - New York Blood Center: Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1997 May 21 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - New York Blood Center: Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1997 October 22 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - New York Blood Center: Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1998 January 21 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - New York Blood Center: Meetings of the Executive Committee, 1997 December 18 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - New York Blood Center: Meetings of the Executive Committee, 1997 September 25 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - New York Blood Center: Meetings of the Executive Committee, Minutes, 1997 July 22 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - New York Blood Center: Meetings of the Executive Committee, Minutes, 1997 June 19 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - New York Blood Center: Meetings of the Executive Committee, Minutes, 1997 April 24 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - New York Blood Center: Meetings of the Executive Committee, Minutes, 1997 March 27 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - New York Blood Center: Meetings of the Executive Committee, Minutes, 1997 February 27 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - New York Blood Center: Complaint and Consent Decree, 1996 December (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - New York Blood Center: Development Committee, 1995-1998 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - New York Blood Center: Operating Budget and Financial Results, 1995-1996 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - New York Blood Center: Operating Budget and Financial Results, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - New York Blood Center: Publications and Technology, 1994-1997 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - New York Blood Center: Biocyte Correspondence and License Agreements, 1992-1993 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - New York Blood Center: Melville Biologics, 1993-1994 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Biocyte Board Lists and Information, 1989-1991 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Biocyte Correspondence, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Biocyte Correspondence, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Biocyte Correspondence, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Biocyte Correspondence, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Biocyte Correspondence, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Biocyte Correspondence, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Biocyte Correspondence, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Biocyte Correspondence, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Biocyte Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Biocyte Correspondence, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Biocyte Correspondence, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Biocyte Correspondence, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Biocyte Correspondence, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Biocyte (PharmaStem) Correspondence, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Biocyte (PharmaStem) Correspondence, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Biocyte (PharmaStem) Correspondence, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Phelps Capital Campaign Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Phelps Capital Campaign Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Phelps Planning Committee, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Phelps Correspondence, 1992; 1994 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Phelps Correspondence, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Phelps Correspondence, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Phelps Correspondence, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Contributions, 1954-1960 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Contributions, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Contributions, 1962 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Contributions, 1963-1964 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Contributions, 1965-1966 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Contributions, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Contributions, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Contributions, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Contributions, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Contributions, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Contributions, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Contributions, 1973-1974 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Contributions, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Contributions, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Contributions, 1977-1978 (Box 42, Folder 2-3)
  - Contributions, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Contributions, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Contributions, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Contributions, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Contributions, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Contributions, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Contributions, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Contributions, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Contributions, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Contributions, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Contributions, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Contributions, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Contributions, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Contributions, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Contributions, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Contributions, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Contributions, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Contributions, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Contributions, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Contributions, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Contributions, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Contributions, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Contributions, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Contributions, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Contributions, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Contributions, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Contributions, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Contributions, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Contributions, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Contributions, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Contributions, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Contributions, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Contributions, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Contributions, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Contributions, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Contributions, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Contributions, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Contributions, 1999 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Contributions, 1999 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Contributions, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Charitable Contributions, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Charitable Contributions, 1972-1982 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Charitable Contributions, 1972-1982 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Contribution Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Contribution Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Matching Gifts Education Program, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 25)